A Guide to the Papers of the Nevins-Perkins-Griswold Family of Connecticut, 1731-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Correspondence and Loose Papers
  - [Joseph] Perkins to his mother 1866 Nov. 9, 2 p. ALS.
  - Charges for school, Marian Nevins 1867 Sept. 16, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, David H. Nevins to Thomas P. Nevins 1868 Jan. 20, 1 p. DS.
  - Appointment as Guardian, David H. Nevins 1868 Jan. 20, 1 p. DS.
  - Charges for school, Marian Nevins 1869 Sept. 20, 1 p. DS.
  - Deed, David H. Nevins to Henry E. Hobron 1872 Jan. 22, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Henry E. Hobron to David H. Nevins 1872 Jan. 22, 2 p. DS.
  - Henry W. [Bellows] to Louisa Nevins 1872 Aug. 19, 4 p. ALS.
  - Deed, Thomas P. Nevins to Russell A. Nevins 1872 Sept. 16, 3 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Samuel Williams to David H. Nevins 1873 Sept. 29, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Russell A. Nevins to David H. Nevins 1874 Jan. 10, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Russell A. Nevins to Marian G., Cornelia L., and Anna L. Nevins 1874 Jan. 10, 3 p. ADS.
  - Katie [?] to Anna [?] 1881 Apr. 4, 4 p. ALS.
  - "Exercises in Composition" [ca. 1881] Feb.-May, 12 p. AM.
  - Katie [?] to "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] 1882 Mar. 21, 4 p. AL(fragment).
  - [?] to her mother [1882] Oct. 9, 19 p. AL(fragment).
  - [A. L.] Nevins to "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] [1885] Mar. 29, 8 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Jan. 31, 6 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Feb. 14, 8 p. ALS.
  - Anna Louisa Nevins to her cousins [1886] Mar. 1, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to Louisa [?] [1886] Mar. 14, 6 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Mar. 21, 4 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Apr. 4, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins [1886] Apr. 11, 6 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Apr. 18, 4 p. ALS.
  - Anna Louisa [Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Apr. 25, 6 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 May 3, 4 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 May 17, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins [1886 May] 24, 6 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 May 29, 8 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1886 June 7, 6 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 June 13, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1886 July 5, 6 p. ALS (fragment).
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 July 11, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1886 July 14, 8 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 July 26, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Aug. 2, 6 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Aug. 9, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Aug. 16, 7 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1886 Sept. 5, 6 p. ALS(fragment).
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins eonclosing AL (fragment) from ["Nina", i.e. Cornelia Nevins] 1886 Oct. 24, 8 p. 2 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Jan. 16, 8 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins ca. 1887 Jan. 1, 4 p. ALS(fragment).
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Jan. [31], 10 p. ALS.
  - Anna [Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Feb. 13, 10 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Feb. 21, 7 p. ALS.
  - Anna L. Nevins to her cousins [1887] Feb. 29, 8 p. ALS.
  - ["Nina", i.e. Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Mar. 5, 8 p. AL(fragment).
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Mar. 13, 6 p. ALS.
  - ["Nina", i.e. Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Mar. 19, 2 p. AL(fragment).
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Mar. 27, 4 p. AL(fragment).
  - fragments of letters from ["Nina", i.e. Cornelia Nevins] and Anna L. Nevins ca. 1887 Mar., 8 p. 4 items.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Apr. 17, 4 p. ALS.
  - Anna L. Nevins to her cousins 1887 May 9, 6 p. 2 p. ALS.
    w/fragment
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1887 May 15, 4 p. ALS.
  - Anna [Nevins] to her cousins 1887 June 27, 4 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Aug. 7, 7 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Aug. 30, 4 p. ALS(fragment).
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Sept. 4, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Sept. 11, 4 p. ALS(fragment).
  - A[nna L.] Nevins to her cousins 1887 Sept. 25, 6 p. ALS.
  - [Anna L. Nevins] to her cousins 1887 Oct. 17, 4 p. ALS.
  - John E. [Kenly] to her Miss Nevins 1890 Dec. 2, 2 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to Anna [Nevins] 1892 Jan. 25, 4 p. ALS.
  - Woodrow Wilson to [Louisa] Perkins 1894 Oct. 1, 2 p. ALS.
  - Theodore Roosevelt to L[ouisa]S. Perkins 1894 Oct. 23, 1 p. TLS.
  - A[nna] L. Nevins to "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] 1903 Dec. 28, 12 p. ALS.
  - C[ornelia] L. N[evins] to Anna L. Nevins 1904 Sept. 30, APCS.
  - Charles P. Paulding to Miss Nevins 1905 Jan. 23, 3 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to [Anna L. Nevins] 1906 Feb. 12, 4 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to [Anna L. Nevins] [ca. 1906 Feb.], 4 p. ALS.
  - "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] to [Anna L. Nevins] [ca. 1906 Feb.], 4 p. ALS(fragment).
  - ["Nina", i.e. Cornelia Nevins] to [Anna L. Nevins] [ca. 1906 Feb.], 4 p. ALS(fragment).
  - S. Baring [Guild] to "Madam" 1910 Oct. 21, 1 p. ALS.
  - [?] to "Aunt Lulie" and "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] 1918 Jan. 7, 4 p. AL(fragment).
  - Anna L. Nevins to "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins] [1918] Aug. 4, 3 p. ALS.
  - [?] to Norris Nevins [1924] May 8, APC.
  - Chandler Starr to [?] [1926 Mar.], 1 p. TLS(frgament).
    w/note by Anna L. Nevins
  - Chandler Starr to Anna L. Nevins 1926 Apr. 10, 1 p. TLS.
  - J. Ramsey MacDonald to Miss Perkins 1930 Sept. 7, 3 p. ALS, w/envelope
  - [Isabel] McDonald to Miss Perkins 1930 Sept. 13, 2 p. ALS, w/envelope
  - J. Ramsey MacDonald to Miss Perkins 1937 Nov. 2, 3 p. TLS.
  - Herbert P. Brigham to Anna L. Nevins 1942 Mar. 4, 1 p. TL(copy).
  - Zara Jones Powers to Anna L. Nevins 1942 Mar. 13, 1 p. TLS.
  - Mary G. B[?] to Mrs. Clarence A. Carr [1949] Aug. 7, APCS.
  - Harry Barnard to Mrs. Hale 1950 Apr. 10, 1 p. TLS.
  - Harry Barnard to Miss Nevins 1950 Apr. 27, 1 p. TLS.
  - Harry Barnard to Miss Nevins 1950 July 5, 1 p. TLS.
  - Rebecca [?] to [?] 1950 Nov. 19, 2 p. ALS.
  - Harry Barnard to Miss Nevins 1950 Dec. 18, 1 p. TLS.
  - [L.A. McLeod] to Anna Nevins (on verson of price list) 1951 Jan. 5, 1 p. 1 p. TL.
  - Rosemary Park to Anna L. Nevins 1953 July 2, 1 p. TLS.
  - Louise [Wilson] to Anna Nevins [1955] Aug. 1, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Russell [?] to "Grandmother and Aunt Fan" 1964 Feb. 17, 2 p. ALS.
- Correspondence and Loose Papers
  (Untitled Items)
  - C[harles] P. Paulding to Miss Nevins [? yr] Mar. 18, 2 p. ALS.
  - John LaFarge to "Dear Madam" [? yr] Apr. 9, 1 p. ALS.
  - C[hester] A. Arthur to Louisa E. Nevins [? yr] Apr. 17, 3 p. ALS.
  - Felix Adler to Miss Perkins [? yr] Oct. 1, 2 p. ALS.
  - [Anna Nevins?] to Louisa [Nevins] n.d. Sunday, 4 p. AL.
  - Th[omas]S. P[erkins] to Mary [Perkins] n.d. Sunday, 1 p. ALS.
  - "Byrd" to [?] n.d., 2 p. ALS.
  - Lucy [?] to "Grandmother and Aunt Fan" n.d., 2 p. ALS.
  - Thomas S. Perkins to N. S. Perkins and Th[omas] W. Williams n.d., 1 p. ALS(copy).
  - fragments of letters n.d., 18 p. 5 items.
  - autograph of Chester A. Arthur n.d., 1 p. 1 item.
  - notes re: correspondence n.d., 3 p. AM.
  - "The Dying Christian - An Ode" w/typescript copy n.d., 3 p. 4 p. AM.
  - "An Appendix Containing a Brief View of the Life and Character of Mrs. Woodbridge...by Dr. Simon Wolcott" n.d., 14 p. 9 p. AM.
    w/typescript copy
  - Geneology of Harris family (in verse) by J. Harris n.d. [ante 1796], 4 p. 3 p. AM.
  - notes by Anna [?] re: brocade from wedding dress of Temperance Shaw w/typescript copy n.d., 1 p. 1 p. AM.
- Correspondence and Loose Papers
  (Typescript Copies)
  - M. Griswold to Gov. Wolcott 1755 Dec. 16, 2 p. L (copy).
  - Church Membership, Ephraim Woodbridge; Call to pastorate, Ephraim Woodbridge 1768 Apr. 2; 1769 July 5, 1 p. D (copy).
  - E[phraim] Woodbridge to Polly Woodbridge 1770 Oct. 16, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Nathaniel Shaw, Jr. to his mother 1776 Mar. 18, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Louisa Conway to Lucretia Hubbard 1780 Dec. 4, 2 p. L (copy).
  - Louisa Conway to "Sophia" [Lucretia Hubbard] [1781] Sept. 13, 3 p. L (copy).
  - Louisa Conway to "Sophia" [Lucretia Hubbard] [1781] Oct. 5, 2 p. L (copy).
  - Louisa Conway to "Sophia" [Lucretia Hubbard] [1782] July 17, 5 p. L (copy).
  - Louisa Conway to Lucretia [Hubbard] Tracy [1783] Oct. 7, 3 p. L (copy).
  - [Lucretia Shaw Woodbridge] to [Nathaniel Shaw] 1786 Feb. 11, 2 p. L (copy).
  - T[homas] Shaw to [Lu]cretia Shaw Woodbridge 1787 Feb. 27, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Thomas Shaw to Lucretia [Shaw Woodbridge] 1789 Aug. 4, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[ogers] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1796 Jan. 9, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1796 Mar. 8, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1796 Apr. 8, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1796 Apr. 20, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1797 Dec. 25, 3 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 Mar. 7, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 Mar. 13, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 Apr. 6, 3 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 Apr. 17, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 May 16, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 May 26, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 May 31, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 June 6, 3 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 June 22, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 June 26, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 Dec. 26, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Elias Perkins to [Roger Griswold] 1799 Jan. 8, 3 p. L (copy).
  - Elias Perkins to Lucretia [Perkins] 1800 Oct. 19, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1800 Dec. 14, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1801 Jan. 22, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1801 Feb. 6, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1801 Feb. 8, 2 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1801 Feb. 11(AM), 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1801 Feb. 11(PM), 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1801 Feb. 13, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1801 Feb. 16, 1 p. L (copy).
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1801 Mar. 3, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Rob W[?] to Roger Criswold 1802 Apr. 2, 2 p. L (copy).
  - Joanna Caukins to Nathaniel S. Perkins 1802 July 31, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Elias Perkins to Nathaniel S. Perkins and Thomas S. Perkins 1802 Sept. 11, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Elias Perkins to Nathaniel S. Perkins and Thomas S. Perkins 1802 Dec. 8, 1 p. L (copy).
  - B. DeWitt to Jacob Radcliff 1817 July 29, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Thomas S. Perkins to [Ebenezer Lane] 1824 Oct. 6, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Thomas S. Perkins to [Ebenezer Lane] 1825 Mar. 7, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Thomas S. Perkins to [Charles Griswold] 1830 Feb. 27, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Thomas S. Perkins to [Charles Griswold] 1830 July 17, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Fanny Griswold to her children 1835 Dec. 25, 5 p. L (copy).
  - Thomas S. Perkins to Frances W. Lane 1836 July 14, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Fanny Griswold to Frances [Lane] 1843 Dec. 12, 4 p. L (copy).
  - Fanny Griswold to Frances [Lane] 1847 Jan. 24, 4 p. L (copy).
  - Fanny Griswold to Frances [Lane] 1857 Dec. 1, 4 p. L (copy).
  - Mary A. Perkins to [Frances Anne Lane] 1864 Sept. 24, 2 p. L (copy).
  - Mary Ann Perkins to [Frances Anne Lane] 1865 Oct. 21, 2 p. L (copy).
  - M. Griswold to W. G. Lane n.d., 1 p. L (copy).
  - [Ephraim Woodbridge] to Polly [Mary] Shaw n.d., 1 p. L (copy).
  - [Ephraim Woodbridge] to [Mary Shaw] n.d., 2 p. L (copy).
  - Mary Shaw to [Ephraim Woodbridge] n.d., 2 p. L (copy).
  - [Ephraim] Woodbridge to Polly [Mary] Shaw n.d., 1 p. L (copy).
  - E[phraim]; W[oodbridge] to Polly [Mary] Woodbridge n.d., 1 p. L (copy).
  - E[phraim] Woodbridge to Polly Mary [Shaw] Woodbridge [?yr] July 8, 1 p. L (copy).
  - Thomas [Shaw] to Mrs. Temperance Shaw n.d., 1 p. L (copy).
  - [Augustus Henry Griswold] to [Roger Griswold] n.d., 6 p. L (copy, incomplete).
  - Gravestone inscriptions and notes re: Daniel Rogers, Mary Rogers, and Nathaniel Rogers n.d., 3 p. D (copy).
  - "Books in Yale College Library...." n.d., 8 p. TM.
  - "List of Friends who read or studied with me" n.d., 3 p. TM.
  - list of boats and owners n.d., 4 p. TM.
  - poem "For Holly - Rue" n.d., 1 p. TM.
- Correspondence and Loose Papers, Photocopies from Original in [Yale University Library]
  - Bank draft, Ebenezer Huntington to David Nevins 1781 Dec. 27, 1 p. DS.
  - Roger Griswold to Fanny Griswold 1796 Jan. 9, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny [Griswold] 1798 May 26, 2 p. ALS.
  - R[oger] Griswold to Fanny Griswold 1801 Jan. 22, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - James Forrestal to Henry B. Nevins 1943 Feb. 12, 1 p. TLS.
- Diplomas and Certificates
  - Yale College to Thomas Shaw Perkins 1815 Sept. 14, DS.
  - Yale College to G. Perkins 1816 Sept. 20, DS.
  - American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions to Thomas Shaw Perkins 1837 Aug. 19, DS.
  - The University Society Inc. to Mrs. G. E. Smith 1924 Nov. 10, D.
- Photographs
  - tintype of unidentified woman n.d.
    1.
  - Carte de Visite of unidentified woman by Edward P. Hipple, Philadelphia. n.d.
    2.
  - Carte de Visite of "Aunt Emily - Mrs. [Rogers Hoffner]" by George G. Rockwood, New York. n.d.
    3.
  - 2 photographs of portrait of unidentified woman. n.d.
    4.
  - photograph of unidentified woman and child n.d.
    5.
  - Carte de Visite of "The Actress Rachel- My [Mother] Cornelia Perkins was supposed to bear a resemblance as to the upper part of her face - A[nna] L. N[evins]" n.d.
    6.
  - photograph, "Little White House" n.d.
    7.
  - photograph, "Proposed residence for Mr. and Mrs. R. G. Nevins" n.d.
    8.
  - photograph, Lea Esmonde, Lady Esmonde, Osmond Esmonde, Russell Nevins, John March (at Shaw Farm) 1926
    9.
  - photogrpah, Lady Esmonde, "Nina" [Cornelia Nevins], [Osmond Esmonde], Russell [Nevins], Anna [L. Nevins], John March [at Shaw Farm] [1926]
    10.
  - photograph of "The Summer House [at] Shaw Farm - rejuvenated by R. H. N[evins] in the summer of 1935 and destroyed in hurricane of 1938" 1935 Nov.
    11.
  - photogrpah of "Anna L. Nevins taken at [Lyme] Hospital..." 1954 Jan.
    12.
- Bound Volumes
  - Cash Journal, unidentified 1842 May 23 - 1843 Sept. 30, 572 p.
  - Account Journal, The Estate of Russell H. Nevins in Account with D[avid] H. Nevins, executor 1854 Feb. 3 - 1882 July 1, 152 p.
  - Scrapbook, kept by [Cornelia L. Nevins], consisting largely of theatre advertisements, literary articles, and clothing fashions ca. 1875-1877, 75 p (pp. 40-65 blank) p.
  - Scrapbook, kept by C[ornelia] L. Nevins [and others], consisting largely of theatre advertisements, literary articles, and articles re: Henry B. Nevins and his boat construction company, and Marian Nevins MacDowell ca. 1873-1954, 101 p.
  - Loose-leaf volume, "A Melancholy of my own," typescript memoirs (in part copies of letters) of [L.S.W. Perkins] containing information re: the Nevins, Perkins, and Griswold family, ca. 1860- 1925. ca. 1912-1926, 105 p.
- Printed Material
  - Broadside, "An Act for the Government and Regulation of Seamen in the Merchant's Service". Signed by crew of Allyn Mather's Schooner "Frolic." 1790 July 20, 2 p.
  - Newspaper, Alexandria Gazette Commercial and Political[Alexandria, Va.] 1813 June 24, 4 p.
  - Newspaper, The Republican Advocate(New London, Connecticut) 1818 Aug. 12, 4 p.
  - Newspaper, Arkansas Times and Advocate(Little Rock, Arkansas) 1837 Nov. 13, 4 p.
  - Bound Volume, Contributions of CC., Now Declared in Full as Criticus Criticorum(Brown & Parsons, Hartford [Conn.]) [Religious essays published at request of Thomas S. Perkins, et al] 1849, 60 p.
  - Monograph, Bride Brook, A Legend of New London, Connecticut, by Miss F. M. Caulkins (Colfax & Holt, New London, [Conn.]) 1852, 11 p.
  - "Map of the Southern States...Presented to the Subscribers of The Sun" (Baltimore, Maryland) 1862 Jan. 4, 1 p.
  - Monograph, In Memoriam - Miss Frances Manwaring Caulkins - A Sermon..., by Rev. G. B. Willcox(Ruddock & Tibbits, New London [Conn.]) 1869 Feb. 14, 12 p.
  - Monograph, Memoir of Frances Manwaring Caulkins by Henry P. Haven(reprint by David Clapp & son, Boston [Mass.]) 1869, 17 p.
  - Bound Volume, Obituary Record of Graduates of Yale College... 1877, 42 p.
  - Printed Card, "With Greetings for Christmas and New Year" [from] J. Ramsey MacDonald 1929-30, 2 p.
  - Monograph, Griswold Family Research in England, by Charles C. Griswold [1931], 12 p.
  - Bound volume, incomplete, A Funeral Sermon(pp. 11-[34]), containing "An Appendix, Containing a Brief View of the Life and Character of Mrs. Woodbridge by Another Hand" (9p) and "The Dying Christrian, An Ode, Occassioned by Meditating on the State of Mrs. Woodbridge's Mind Before Her Death" (3p) [Note: the latter two essays are microfilmed in original manuscript. See "correspondence and Loose Papers - Undated Items" above] n.d.
  - Bound volume, Martha, Daughter of Mehetabel Chandler Coit, 1706-1784 (Bulletin Print, Norwich, Conn.) 1895, 33 p.
  - Monograph, Married at Woodstock, Conn., June 25, 1695...John Coit and Mehitable daughter of Deacon John and Elizabeth (Douglass) Chandler, with "A letter from Mehitable Coit to her daughter Martha" [1726 May 19] n.d., 18 p.
  - Newsclipping, obituary of Chandler Starr ([?], Rockford, Illinois) 1930 Oct. 10, 1 p.
  - Program of the Unveiling of a Bronze Tablet...Shaw Mansion, New London, Connecticut 1933 Aug. 19, 4 p.
  - Newspaper, The Concord Journal[containing article re: Lucretia Shaw and Woodbridge Perkins] 1938 May 26, 2 p.
  - Newsclipping, obituary of Henry Nevins ( New York Times) 1950 Dec. 7, 1 p.
  - Newsclipping, obituary of Henry Nevins ( New York Tribune) 1950 Dec. 7, 1 p.